<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="title_me">Me</string>
    <string name="content_me">
        I\'m Denley (That\'s me to the right).
        I was born, raised, and educated in Adelaide, Australia.
        I want to lead the Android charge at Basecamp™.
    </string>

    <string name="title_heart">At Heart</string>
    <string name="content_heart">
        I\'m into technology and gadgets (I\'m <![CDATA[<b><i>really</i></b>]]> into gadgets).
        I enjoy looking at
        <![CDATA[<a href="https://www.kickstarter.com/discover/advanced?category_id=16&sort=newest">
        new technology projects</a>]]>
        on Kickstarter™, and reading about the
        <![CDATA[<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Consumer_Electronics_Show">CES</a>]]>
        every year. I also like reading anything scientific or technical.
        <![CDATA[<br/><br/>]]>
        In my spare time I like watching sci-fi, and working on my own Android™ app ideas
        (including apps for my Android Wear smartwatch).
        I play pool (billiards) in a team with friends.
    </string>

    <string name="title_trade">By Trade</string>
    <string name="content_trade">
        I\'m a professional Android guru (freelance Android developer).
        I work with clients all over the world to:
        <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
        1) Build app ideas from scratch
        <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
        2) Update existing apps (fixing bugs and updating designs)
        <![CDATA[<br/>]]>
        3) Port existing iOS apps over to Android
        (while trying hard to convince them to adapt their designs)
        <![CDATA[<br/><br/>]]>
        I really enjoy what I do.
        I like the cutting-edge and open nature of the Android community.
        I like the variety of projects that keep me challenged and engaged.
        I like the freedom to work remotely and manage my own time.
        But most of all, I like that every single day I am pushed to learn new skills,
        improve existing ones, and keep up to date with the latest in the Android platform.
    </string>

    <string name="title_aspiration">To The Future</string>
    <string name="content_aspiration">
        First and foremost, I want to continue to work with the Android platform, whether
        continuing as a freelancer, or as an employee working on Android projects.

        \n\nI would like to work on products that I would find useful myself,
        and to work thoroughly rather than quickly,
        so that I can be proud of my results.

        \n\nI want to surround myself with talented people whom I can respect and commend,
        who will push me to be my best and refine my skills,
        and who aren\'t too polite to let me know how I can improve.
    </string>

</resources>