<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="author1">Graham Dawson</string>
    <string name="quote1">
        Denley is what I would call a Ninja developer.
        He\'s at the top of the game - at least 3 times more
        efficient than someone who charges 1/2 the hourly rate.
        I couldn\'t be more pleased with his work,
        and it\'s been nothing but a pleasure to work with him.
    </string>

    <string name="author2">Alex Daniel</string>
    <string name="quote2">
        Fantastic developer. Continual communication,
        educated opinion and happy to work towards 100% satisfaction.
        I recommend Denley for any Android app job where quality and updatability is required.
        Code is clean, well thought-out and well commented. Adheres to good programming practices
        and was happy to fix any bugs and interface issues as they arose without complaint.
        Very happy with this project, developer and final deliverable
    </string>

    <string name="author3">Eric C</string>
    <string name="quote3">
        Denley is a true professional, with solid Android knowledge and a great attention to detail.
        Count on him to produce a high quality, well thought out app.
        He did a fantastic job on my project, meeting all the requirements (even more!)
        and replied quickly to my requests/feedbacks. The highest recommendation for promptness,
        responsiveness, communication, expertise and quality of work.
        A top choice for any Android app development, worth every penny.
        I\'m very impressed, I can\'t say enough positive things. Just awesome, will hire again.
    </string>

    <string name="author4">Sam Hu</string>
    <string name="quote4">
        Denley has been excellent in working on this android app.
        Great ideas to turn the requirements into reality, great work ethic, great support.
        Communication and response times very good. Highly recommended.
    </string>

    <string name="author5">Sergey Berezin</string>
    <string name="quote5">
        Denley is really the sort of developer you are seldom to meet:
        \n1) he understands what is important and what isn\'t
        \n2) he likes what he does and takes the responsibility for it
    </string>

</resources>