<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="title_why">Why Basecamp?</string>

    <string name="title_you">You</string>
    <string name="content_you">
        At Basecamp you aren\'t afraid to break norms. Instead of relying on conventions, you
        literally <![CDATA[<a href="http://gettingreal.37signals.com/">wrote the book</a>]]>
        about running a web business.
        <![CDATA[<br/><br/>]]>

        You\'ve made great products, that have earned you the respect of the web community.
        You don\'t try to do everything. But what you do, you do well.
    </string>

    <string name="title_this_job">Your New Android Lead</string>
    <string name="content_this_job">
        You\'re looking for somebody who lives and breathes Android, but you\'re also a
        relatively small team. This means that you\'d rather somebody well-rounded than
        specialised. So you want a quick learner, who is engaged and flexible when trying
        new things and wearing many hats.
        <![CDATA[<br/><br/>]]>

        You want someone that clicks with your team, but also not too shy to break the norm
        and provide new ways of solving problems. You want someone who sees what they do as
        a passion, not a chore.
    </string>

    <string name="title_a_perfect_fit">A Perfect Fit</string>
    <string name="content_a_perfect_fit">
        I believe that my experience and aspirations are a great fit for your company,
        and your new position of lead Android developer.
        <![CDATA[<br/><br/>]]>

        I am enthusiastic and capable to take on the variety of tasks that this role
        will require. Unlike
        <![CDATA[<a href="http://www.reddit.com/r/androiddev/comments/2t7rba/job_lead_android_at_basecamp_work_anywhere/cnwyr7x">other developers</a>]]>
        who
        <![CDATA[<a href="http://www.reddit.com/r/androiddev/comments/2t7rba/job_lead_android_at_basecamp_work_anywhere/cnxupxw">respond</a>]]>
        to your job postings, I welcome participation in your
        <![CDATA[<a href="https://signalvnoise.com/posts/3676-everyone-on-support">
        Everyone on Support</a>]]> programme.
        As a full-time freelancer, I spend a lot of time working directly with customers in order
        to understand their requirements and resolve their issues. I appreciate and enjoy the
        perspective that this provides. Eliciting and understanding use-cases directly from
        customers is the only way to effectively develop and refine design and implementation
        criteria.
        <![CDATA[<br/><br/>]]>

        I am ready to take the new challenges that this role will provide. Basecamp\'s Android
        app has been downloaded by hundreds of thousands of users. This means that the role requires
        great attention to detail, and a strength to absorb the scrutiny that the work will
        inevitably attract. It will be tough, but it will be worth it. It will help me push my
        skills to the next level.
    </string>

</resources>